Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Role-Playing Games, 1972-2017 RL.00924
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Boxed Games, 1972-2007; 82 boxes
  - General Games, 66
    - The Lords of Underearth (Metagaming), 1980 (Box BG63)
      MicroGame 18
    - The Plot to Assassinate Hitler, 1940-1945 (Simulations Publications, Inc.), 1976 (Box BG64)
      Power Politics Series Historical Simulation Game
    - The Punic Wars: Rome vs. Carthage, 264-146 B.C. (Simulations Publications, Inc.), 1975 (Box BG39)
    - The Roaring 20's: A Game of Gangsters (Yaquinto Publications), 1981 (Box BG57)
    - The Sorcerer's Cave (Ariel), 1978 (Box BG57)
    - The Sword and the Stars (Simulations Publications, Inc.), 1981 (Box BG51)
    - The Thieves' World: Complete Sanctuary Adventure Pack (Chaosium Inc.), 1981 (Box BG62)
      Designed for use with 9 role-playing systems
    - The Trojan War: The Game of Gods and Heroes (Metagaming), 1981 (Box BG58)
      MetaHistory 2
    - The Valley of the Pharaoh: Role Playing Adventure in Ancient Egypt (Palladium Books), 1983 (Box BG40)
    - The War of the Worlds (Task Force Games), 1980 (Box BG56)
    - The Warlord Game (Robert Williams Games), 1976 (Box BG35)
    - Thieves Guild (Gamelords), 1984 (Box BG73)
    - Time & Time Again: The Time Travel Role Playing Game (Timeline Ltd.), 1984 (Box BG22)
    - Time Master: Adventures in the 4th Dimension (Pacesetter), 1984 (Box BG24)
    - Time Tripper (Simulations Publications, Inc.), 1980 (Box BG41)
    - Time War (Yaquinto Publications), 1979 (Box BG29)
    - Timeship: A role playing game of time travel and adventure (Yaquinto Publications), 1983 (Box BG22)
    - Trailblazer (Metagaming), 1981 (Box BG63)
      MicroGame 20
    - Treasure of the Silver Dragon (Metagaming), 1980 (Box BG63)
      MicroQuest 4
    - Treasure of Unicorn Gold (Metagaming), 1981 (Box BG56)
      MicroQuest 6
    - Triplanetary: Space Combat in the Solar System 2001 (Game Designers' Workshop), 1981 (Box BG37)
    - Twilight: 2000 (Game Designers' Workshop), 1984 (Box BG41)
    - Valley of the Four Winds: An Epic Game of Swords and Sorcery (Games Workshop Ltd), 1980 (Box BG42)
    - Villians and Vigilantes (Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1982 (Box BG25)
    - Wabbit Wampage (Pacesetter), 1985 (Box BG19)
    - Warlocks & Warriors: Introductory Level (TSR, Inc.), 1977 (Box BG46)
    - Wild West: A Role Playing Game Set in the Old West (Fantasy Games Unlimited), 1981 (Box BG20)
    - Witch Hunt: Role Playing: Salem 1692 (Statcom Simulations Inc.), 1983 (Box BG22)
    - Worlds of Wonder (Chaosium Inc.), 1982 (Box BG39)
- Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes, 1973-2011; 2399 Volumes
  The Modules, Manuals, and Campaign Volumes series includes books designed to accompany or enable role-playing in a variety of worlds. A volume typically includes campaign settings, character guides, game system rules, or reference tools for players. Worlds represented in this series include Dungeons and Dragons, Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, Birthright, Cyberpunk, Call of Cthulhu, Dragon Lance, Earthdawn, Forgotten Realms, Middle Earth, Ravenloft, Spell Jammer, and many more.
  Most volumes are individually numbered and barcoded, unless they included extra components that required them to be housed in a box. There are 6 boxes of volumes (M1-M6) included in this series. All volumes (regardless of volume or box number) have been arranged by alphabetically by game world, then chronologically by date. General volumes that have no identifiable "world" are listed at the end in alphabetical order. A spreadsheet is available for researchers who are interested in sorting the games in a different way.
  - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons, 1
    - A Hero's Tale (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 840)
    - A Mighty Fortress: Campaign Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 895)
    - A Paladin in Hell (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 935)
    - Advanced Dungeons and Dragons 2nd Edition: Preview (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 1777)
    - Adventure Pack I (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 899)
    - Against the Cult of the Reptile God (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 1244)
    - Age of Heroes: Campaign Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 893)
    - All That Glitters (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 488)
    - Arms and Equipment Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 955)
    - Assault on the Aerie of the Slave Lords (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1259)
    - Baltron's Beacon (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 482)
    - Bastion of Faith (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 947)
    - Beyond the Crystal Cave (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1242)
    - Black Opal Eye (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 589)
    - Book of Artifacts (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 564)
    - Campaign Sourcebook and Catacomb Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 953)
    - Castle Sites (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 842)
    - Celts: Campaign Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 896)
    - Character Codex (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1771)
    - Character Record Sheets (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 903)
    - Charlemagne's Paladins: Campaign Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 897)
    - Chronomancer (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 519)
    - City Sites (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 843)
    - College of Wizardry (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 822)
    - Conan: Against Darkness! (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 584)
    - Conan: Unchained! (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 585)
    - Country Sites (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 841)
    - Creative Campaigning (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 948)
    - Danger at Dunwater (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1277)
    - Dark and Hidden Ways: For Immediate Play with the Dungeoneer's Survival Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 592)
    - Dark Clouds Gather (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 487)
    - Dark Folk: Trolls, Orcs, Goblins, Kobolds, Gnolls (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1624)
    - Dark Tower: Fantasy Game Aid (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1566)
    - Day of Al'Akbar (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 479)
    - Deities and Demigods (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 640)
    - Den of Thieves (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 808)
    - Descent into the Depths of the Earth (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1253)
    - Destiny of Kings (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 491)
    - Die Vecna Die! (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 799)
    - Doc's Island (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 610)
    - Dragon Lance: Adventures (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 641)
    - Dragon's Hall (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1484)
    - Dragons (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1986 (Volume 1309)
    - Dragons of Weng T'Sen (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1304)
    - Dungeon Builder's Guidebook (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 942)
    - Dungeon Master Option: High-Level Campaigns (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 582)
    - Dungeon Master Screen and Master Index (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 574)
    - Dungeon Master's Design Kit (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 904)
    - Dungeon Master's Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 563)
    - Dungeon Master's Screen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1639)
    - Dungeon Master's Screen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 615)
    - Dungeon Masters Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 573)
    - Dungeon Masters Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 1757)
    - Dungeon Masters Screen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 1640)
    - Dungeoneer's Survival Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 570)
    - Dungeonland (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1247)
    - Dungeons of Despair (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 941)
    - Dwarves (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1982 (Volume 1625)
    - Dwellers of the Forbidden City (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1250)
    - Egg of the Phoenix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 480)
    - Encyclopedia Magica, Volume 1 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 957)
    - Encyclopedia Magica, Volume 2 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 958)
    - Encyclopedia Magica, Volume 3 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 959)
    - Encyclopedia Magica, Volume 4 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 960)
    - Escape from Astigar's Lair (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1509)
    - Evil Ruins (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1303)
    - Expedition to the Barrier Peaks (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1273)
    - Eye of the Serpent (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 489)
    - Fantastic Treasures (Chicago, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1984 (Volume 1669)
    - Fantastic Treasures II (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1985 (Volume 1644)
    - Fiend Folio: Tome of Creatures Malevolent and Benign (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 639)
    - Fighter's Screen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 575)
    - Guide to Hell (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1006)
    - Hall of the Fire Giant King (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1254)
    - House on Hangman's Hill (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1483)
    - In the Dungeons of the Slave Lords (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1249)
    - Inferno (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1506)
    - Labyrinth of Madness (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 521)
    - Lara's Tower (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1494)
    - Legends and Lore (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 566)
    - Lich Lords (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1985 (Volume 1307)
    - Lost Tomb of Martek (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 483)
    - Manual of the Planes (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 572)
    - Midnight on Dagger Alley (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1135)
    - Monster Manual II (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 561)
    - Monster Manual: An Illustrated Compendium of Monsters (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1977 (Volume 560)
    - Monster Mythology (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 956)
    - Monsters of Myth and Legend (Chicago, IL: Mayfair Games), 1984 (Volume 1641)
    - Monsters of Myth and Legend II (Chicago, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1989 (Volume 1653)
    - Monstrous Compendium Annual, Vol. 1 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 1782)
    - Monstrous Compendium Annual, Vol. 2 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 1783)
    - Monstrous Compendium Annual, Vol. 3 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 1784)
    - Monstrous Compendium Annual, Vol. 4 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1998 (Volume 1785)
    - Moonlight Madness (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 937)
    - Non-Player Character Records (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1763)
    - Oasis of the White Palm (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 484)
    - Of Ships and the Sea (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 949)
    - Oriental Adventures (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 569)
    - Permenant Character and Adventure Records (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 1760)
    - Pharaoh (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 485)
    - Pinnacle (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1986 (Volume 1299)
    - Player Character Record Sheets (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 1762)
    - Player Character Record Sheets (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1761)
    - Player Character Record Sheets (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 1759)
    - Player's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1758)
    - Player's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 567)
    - Player's Option: Combat and Tactics (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 580)
    - Player's Option: Skills and Powers (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 581)
    - Player's Option: Spells and Magic (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 579)
    - Players Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 568)
    - Portals of Irontooth (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1534)
    - Portals of Torsh (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1980 (Volume 1568)
    - Portals of Twilight (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1535)
    - Priest's Screen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 576)
    - Priest's Spells Compendium Vol. 1 (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1779)
    - Priest's Spells Compendium Vol. 2 (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1780)
    - Priest's Spells Compendium Vol. 3 (Renton, WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 1781)
    - Queen of the Demonweb Pits (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1278)
    - Queen of the Spicers (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 1263)
    - Rahasia (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 590)
    - Ravager of Time (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 481)
    - Ravenloft: A Guide to Transylvania (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 637)
    - Realms of Horror (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 1270)
    - Red Sonja Unconquered (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 586)
    - Reverse Dungeon (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 946)
    - Sages and Specialists (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 950)
    - Scourge of the Slavelords (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 1262)
    - Secret of the Slavers Stockade (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1258)
    - Shadows of Evil (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1984 (Volume 1301)
    - Shaman (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 520)
    - Shipwrecker (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1300)
    - Shrine of the Kuo-Toa (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1252)
    - Slave Pits of the Undercity (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1257)
    - Steading of the Hill Giant Chief (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1256)
    - Swordthrust (Chicago, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1984 (Volume 1294)
    - Tales of the Outer Planes (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 902)
    - Temple of Ra Accursed by Set (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1508)
    - The Apocalypse Stone (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 945)
    - The Assassin's Knot (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1240)
    - The Book of Lairs (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 900)
    - The Book of Lairs II (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1987 (Volume 901)
    - The Book of Ruins (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1567)
    - The Castle Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 954)
    - The Complete Barbarian's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 698)
    - The Complete Bard's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 695)
    - The Complete Book of Dwarves (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 701)
    - The Complete Book of Elves (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 702)
    - The Complete Book of Gnomes and Halflings (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 703)
    - The Complete Book of Humanoids (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 704)
    - The Complete Book of Necromancers (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 951)
    - The Complete Book of Villains (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 952)
    - The Complete Druid's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 700)
    - The Complete Fighter's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 690)
    - The Complete Ninja's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 699)
    - The Complete Paladin's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 697)
    - The Complete Priest's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 692)
    - The Complete Psionics Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 694)
    - The Complete Ranger's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 696)
    - The Complete Thief's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1989 (Volume 691)
    - The Complete Wizard's Handbook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 693)
    - The Crusades Campaign Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 802)
    - The Dancing Hut of Baba Yaga (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1995 (Volume 522)
    - The Egg of the Phoenix (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 611)
    - The Elixir of Life (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 587)
    - The Final Enemy (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1276)
    - The Forest Oracle (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 583)
    - The Forgotten King (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 588)
    - The Forgotten Temple of Tharizdun (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 1271)
    - The Gates of Firestorm Peak (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 809)
    - The Gauntlet (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1261)
    - The Ghost Tower of Inverness (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1410)
    - The Glacial Rift of the Frost Giant Jarl (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1255)
    - The Glory of Rome: Campaign Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 894)
    - The Hidden Shrine of Tamoachan (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1980 (Volume 1243)
    - The Illhiedrin Book (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1545)
    - The Investigation of Hydell (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 612)
    - The Keep (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1983 (Volume 1308)
    - The Land Beyond the Magic Mirror (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1246)
    - The Lost Caverns of Tsojcanth (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 1272)
    - The Lost Island of Castanamir (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 1134)
    - The Lost Shrine of Bundushatur (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 938)
    - The Maltese Clue (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1507)
    - The Murky Deep (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1993 (Volume 905)
    - The Secret of Bone Hill (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1241)
    - The Sentinel (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1983 (Volume 1260)
    - The Shattered Circle (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 944)
    - The Silver Key (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 906)
    - The Sinister Secret of Saltmarsh (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1981 (Volume 1280)
    - The Star of Kolhapur (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 936)
    - The Star of Kolhapur (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1997 (Volume 943)
    - The Temple of Elemental Evil (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 1269)
    - The Treasure Vaults of Lindoran (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1979 (Volume 1488)
    - The Village of Hommlet (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 1245)
    - The Vortex of Madness and other planar perils (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 2000 (Volume 1005)
    - Thief's Screen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 577)
    - Throne of Evil (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1984 (Volume 1302)
    - To Find a King (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 614)
    - To the Aid of Falx (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 613)
    - Tomb of Horrors (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1275)
    - Tomb of the Lizard King (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1982 (Volume 486)
    - Tome of Magic (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 565)
    - Tower of Jourdar (Littleton, CO: Dimension Six, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1629)
    - Treasure Chest (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 845)
    - Treasure Maps (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 846)
    - Treasure Tales (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 844)
    - Trial by Fire (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1539)
    - Triviathlon: The Arcane Challenge (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 1791)
      Mail-in game of trivia questions.
    - TSR JAM 1999 (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast) (Volume 940)
    - Undead (Niles, IL: Mayfair Games, Inc. ), 1986 (Volume 1136)
    - Unearthed Arcana (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1985 (Volume 562)
    - Vault of the Drow (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1978 (Volume 1251)
    - Vikings: Campaign Sourcebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1991 (Volume 898)
    - Wand of Archeal (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 939)
    - Warriors of Heaven (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1999 (Volume 1007)
    - When a Star Falls (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1984 (Volume 490)
    - White Plume Mountain (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR Hobbies, Inc.), 1979 (Volume 1274)
    - Wild Things: For Immediate Play with the Wilderness Survival Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1990 (Volume 591)
    - Wilderness Survival Guide (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1986 (Volume 571)
    - Wizard's Screen (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1994 (Volume 578)
    - Wizard's Spell Compendium Vol. 1 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 1786)
    - Wizard's Spell Compendium Vol. 2 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1997 (Volume 1787)
    - Wizard's Spell Compendium Vol. 3 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1998 (Volume 1788)
    - Wizard's Spell Compendium Vol. 4 (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1998 (Volume 1789)
    - World Builder's Guidebook (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1996 (Volume 807)
    - World of Greyhawk: Castle Greyhawk (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1988 (Volume 1248)
    - Zienteck (Decatur, IL: Judges Guild, Inc. ), 1981 (Volume 1499)
  - Advanced Squad Leader, 2
    - Advanced Squad Leader Rules: WWII Tactical Warfare Game System (Baltimore: Avalon Hill Game Company), 1985 (Box M7)
    - ASL Action Pack 1 (Baltimore: Avalon Hill Game Company), undated (Box M7)
    - ASL Action Pack 2 (Baltimore: Avalon Hill Game Company), undated (Box M7)
    - ASL Action Pack 3 (Baltimore: Avalon Hill Game Company), 2007 (Box M7)
    - ASL Action Pack 4 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2008 (Box M7)
    - ASL Action Pack 5 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2008 (Box M7)
    - ASL Action Pack 6 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2010 (Box M7)
    - ASL Journal Issue 2 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2000 (Box M7)
      includes boards, scenarios, pieces
    - ASL Journal Issue 4 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2002 (Box M7)
    - ASL Journal Issue 5 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2003 (Box M7)
    - ASL Journal Issue 6 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2005 (Box M7)
    - ASL Journal Issue 7 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2006 (Box M7)
    - ASL Journal Issue 9 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2011 (Box M7)
    - Out of the Attic Issue 2 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2010 (Box M7)
    - Rule Book, 2nd edition (Baltimore: Avalon Hill Game Company), 2001 (Box M8)
      Binder of boards, scenarios, rules
    - Scenario bundles (various) (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2000s (Box M7)
    - Starter Kit Expansion Pack 1 (Millersville: Multi-Man Publishing), 2010 (Box M7)
  - Al-Qadim, 3
    - Al-Qadim Reunion (Renton WA: Wizards of the Coast), 1998 (Volume 225)
    - Arabian Adventures (Lake Geneva, WI: TSR, Inc.), 1992 (Volume 223)